const Question = [
	{
		id: 1,
		question: 'What is the Affordable Care Act and what does it mean for me?',
		answer: `The Affordable Care Act (ACA) is the United States of America’s health reform law
       enacted in March of 2010. Also called “Obamacare” because it was signed into law by 
       President Barack Obama, the ACA puts in place comprehensive health insurance reforms 
       that rolled out over four years.`,
	},
	{
		id: 2,
		question: 'What happens if I don’t buy health insurance?',
		answer: `Previously, anyone who didn’t buy ACA coverage was required to pay a tax penalty, 
    unless they qualified for an exemption, but that law was changed for 2020. There is now no
     longer an individual penalty for buying ACA-alternative coverage. For more information on 
     exemptions and buying health insurance, click here.`,
	},
	{
		id: 3,
		question: 'What is “Open Enrollment”?',
		answer: `Open enrollment is the period of time during which individuals can buy ACA 
    approved health plans. The open enrollment period to buy health plans is from November 
    1 through December 15. In order to purchase ACA health insurance coverage outside of 
    open enrollment, you need to qualify for a special enrollment period. Click here to find
     out if you’re eligible.`,
	},
	{
		id: 4,
		question: 'How can I buy or change health insurance outside of Open Enrollment?',
		answer: `There are a number of qualifying life events that would make you eligible to
     buy ACA health insurance outside of Open Enrollment. Some events that trigger a special
      enrollment opportunity include: Loss of eligibility for other coverage (such as losing
      your job or losing student health coverage when you graduate) Gaining a dependent 
    (such as getting married, giving birth, or adopting a child) Divorce or legal separation`,
	},
	{
		id: 5,
		question: 'Should I buy insurance through an agent?',
		answer: `Although you are not required to buy individual health insurance through an agent, 
    it is highly recommended. An agent can help you find a health insurance plan which meets your 
    needs as well as budget. Health insurance is an important and complex subject, and all plans 
    are not created equal. Policies are often written in difficult legal terms that most people are
     not accustomed to reading. An agent can help you make sense of the legalese, 
    so you don’t find yourself in financial difficulty down the road.`,
	},
	{
		id: 6,
		question: 'What is a Health Insurance Marketplace or Exchange?',
		answer: `Health Insurance Marketplaces (also called Exchanges) are websites set up for individuals
     to buy health insurance. Each Marketplace features a number of insurance carriers, each offering 
     different health plans. You can shop, compare and buy a health plan for you and your family.
      Premium and cost sharing subsidies are available through the Marketplace, based on income.
       Small businesses can also buy coverage for their employees through the Small Business Health
        Options Program (SHOP) Marketplace. Some Marketplaces will be operated by the state, while 
        others will use the federal health exchange. The terms “on exchange” and “off exchange” refer
         to health plans either available or not available through a Marketplace. Our agents are able
          tosell plans both on and off exchange. Click here for a free quote.`,
	},
	{
		id: 7,
		question: 'Do I have to buy a health plan on the Marketplace or Exchange?',
		answer: `No. The Marketplace (also called the Exchange) is just one of the ways people can shop 
    for individual health insurance. Our agents have access to all health plans,
     both on and off the exchange. Click here for a free quote.`,
	},
	{
		id: 8,
		question: 'What kind of health plans are available under the Affordable Care Act?',
		answer: `There are four basic ACA plans categorized by metallic levels: Bronze, Silver, 
    Gold and Platinum. These four new metal plans are differentiated from another by their 
    actuarial value. Actuarial value refers to the average amount of expenses that would be paid
     for by the member.The higher the actuarial value of a plan, the lower the out-of-pocket costs 
     for the plan member. A Bronze plan covers 60%, Silver 70%, Gold 80% and Platinum 90% of insurance 
     costs. It follows the average premium will be lower for the lower metal plans, and higher for the 
     higher metal plans.`,
	},
	{
		id: 9,
		question: 'How can I find out if a health plan covers my prescription drugs?',
		answer: `Most managed care programs have a site which lists the prescriptions covered in each
     health plan. This list is called a “formulary”. Agents also have access to each
     health plan’s formulary. Click here to speak with a licensed agent.`,
	},
	{
		id: 10,
		question: 'What’s the difference between an HMO and a PPO?',
		answer: `A Health Maintenance Organization (HMO) is a type of health plan that limits coverage
     to a network of doctors who work for or contract with the HMO. An HMO won't cover out-of-network
      doctors except in the case of an emergency. Most HMO plans require patients to have a primary 
      care physician, who then refers the patient to see specialists. HMOs often require members to 
      live or work within its service area.

 A Preferred Provider Organization (PPO) is a health plan that contracts with providers like 
hospitals and doctors to create a network. Providers in the plan’s network are less costly.
 Patients can use providers outside of the network, but for an 
additional cost. PPOs do not require patients to have a primary care physician.`,
	},
	{
		id: 11,
		question: 'What is an HSA?',
		answer: `A Health Savings Account (HSA) is available to tax payers enrolled in a High Deductible 
		Health Plan. A High Deductible Health Plan generally has a lower premium, so the money that you 
		save monthly can then be put into the HSA. HSAs enable you to pay for current health expenses and
		 save for future qualified medical and retiree health expenses on a tax-free basis. If you withdraw 
		 funds for any reason other than qualified medical expenses, the money will become subject to both income
		 tax and a ten percent IRS penalty. (There is one exception, when you become 65 years of age or older, you 
		may then withdraw the money without penalty. The withdrawal will still be subject to income tax.) The money
		 in the HSA account rolls over from year to year, and it’s your money- you control it.`,
	},
	{
		id: 12,
		question: `How can I find if my doctor is in a health plan’s network?`,
		answer: `Most managed care programs have a site which lists the doctors, hospitals and/or facilities included in 
		the PPO or HMO network. Agents also have access to a list of providers in every health plan, so he/she can look up 
		your doctor for you. Click here to speak with a licensed agent.`,
	},
];

export default Question;